<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Redeployment | The Code for Greenville Brigade Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://codeforgreenville.org/blog/categories/redeployment/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://codeforgreenville.org/"/>
  <updated>2014-05-07T17:48:29-04:00</updated>
  <id>http://codeforgreenville.org/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Code for Greenville Brigade]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Redeployment Spotlight Introduction]]></title>
    <link href="http://codeforgreenville.org/blog/2014/05/07/redeployment-spotlight-introduction/"/>
    <updated>2014-05-07T16:33:29-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://codeforgreenville.org/blog/2014/05/07/redeployment-spotlight-introduction</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h1>About Redeployment &amp; The Spotlight Series</h1>

<p>One of the primary goals of the Code for Greenville Brigade is to contribute to the spread of Open Civic Tech. One big way to contribute to the community at large and knock out a quick win as a Brigade is to <strong>Redeploy</strong> other apps that were developed in other cities by other brigades. This allows us to stand on the shoulders of our peers in other cities and gives us an opportunity to improve their work and pay it forward. In the weeks to come we are going to post a series of posts highlighting applications the Code for Greenville Brigade might want to consider redeploying.</p>

<h1>What are we looking for?</h1>

<p>Some key factors we should consider before we redeploy an application:</p>

<ol>
<li>Will this App be helpful to the citizens of greenville?</li>
<li>Will the citizens of greenville use this application?</li>
<li>Has the App been re-deployed by another brigade?</li>
<li>What are the technical depedencies?</li>
<li>What are the data dependencies?</li>
<li>How much does it cost to deploy and maintain?</li>
<li>How can we contribute or improve the app if we deploy it?</li>
</ol>


<h1>How you can help</h1>

<ol>
<li>Take a look at each application. Poke around and see what you think about it.</li>
<li>Then ask yourself &ldquo;Would this app be helpful to me? and "Would I use this App?&rdquo;</li>
<li>Then go ask 2 other greenville citizens the same question. try to pick folks with a different background. see what kind of answers you get.</li>
<li>Now think about Greenville &ndash; what should we consider if we were to deploy this app? Is there something about our town culture or our environment we need to account for or represent?</li>
<li>If your feeling adventurous dive into the apps github site and dive into the code and see what you think.</li>
</ol>


<p>Finally Bring your thoughts back to the <a href="http://www.meetup.com/Code-for-Greenville-Brigade/messages/archive/">meetup discussion</a> or the next <a href="http://www.meetup.com/Code-for-Greenville-Brigade/">meetup</a> and help up decide what apps Code for Greenville will be deploying.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
